OLUWAGBEMIDALE AIYEWUMI

8B OLAYINKA ADEWUYI STREET, U3 ESTATE, LEKKI PHASE 1, LAGOS +234 8097135561, gbemidale.a@gmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Graduate of computer science with experience in Python and full stack web development. I have 4 years of programming with Python and full stack web development including the use of web frameworks such as Vue and React. In order to successfully fill the software developer role, I aim to strengthen my current knowledge of web development, database design and management, and data analysis. Thus I am looking for posts that would grant me the opportunity to grow and learn from more experienced members of the company.

EDUCATION

AMERICAN UNIVERSITY OF NIGERIA

Sept 2017 - Dec 2021

• BSc. Computer Science (C.GPA: 3.6) (1st)

UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS, LOWELL

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

• Electrical Engineering (Before transfer C.GPA ≈ 3.7)

WHITESANDS SECONDARY SCHOOL

• WAEC Certificate acquired

Sept 2007 - Dec 2012

PROJECTS

PLANT CLASSIFICATION USING R-CNN

Sept 2021 - Dec 2021

• The project entailed using a machine learning algorithm to label plant images as either crops or weed. The code was written in Python and made use of data analysis tools such as; seaborn, pandas, matplotlib, TensorFlow and numpy. The model has a 97% accuracy.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERN, Pricewaterhouse Coopers. (PWC)

May 2022 – Feb 2023

- Worked as assistant project manager
- Managed action points from different sections of customer's project

INTERN, STERLING BANK, LAGOS.

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Introduced employees to data analysis tools using python
- Researched into go programming for implementation in the office

INTERN, IKOYI CLUB, LAGOS.

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

- Updated and maintained organization's server
- Assisted in upgrading the transaction processing system for the organization

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Programming languages:** JavaScript, Python
- Frameworks & Libraries: React, Tailwind, Vue, Express, GitHub
- Databases: MySQL, Firebase, MongoDB
- Other skills: JIRA (project management tool)
- Interests: Data science, Data Analysis, Full Stack Development, Machine Learning

Reference Available Upon Request